Fall in love with life again.
Find Me Falling is a romance, comedy, music film directed by Stelana Kliris.
After a failed comeback album, a rock star retreats to a cliffside home on Cyprus,
only to find his new life complicated by visitors — and an old flame.
John Allman, played by Harry Connick Jr..
Sia, played by Agni Scott.
Melina, played by Ali Fumiko Whitney.
Jimmy, played by Clarence Smith.
Anna, played by Athina Roditou.
Petros, played by Antonis Katsaris.
Find Me Falling is a 2024 romantic comedy film
written and directed by Stelana Kliris.
It stars Harry Connick Jr.
as an American rock star who takes a break from his career to live in a remote
house near a cliff in Cyprus, which he discovers is a suicide hotspot.
The cast also includes Agni Scott, Ali Fumiko Whitney, and Clarence Smith.
The film was released by Netflix on July 19, 2024.
It received mixed reviews.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.